Viewers, souls under the bondage, dominion of satan and all his sicknesses and diseases,
receive freedom in the name of Jesus!
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever you are doing at this moment -
are you on the sickbed?
Listen - souls under the bondage, dominion of satan
and all his sicknesses and diseases, setback, disappointment -
receive freedom in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered!
Be healed!
Be set free!
In the name of Jesus!
I believe!
I say, I believe - you will see!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World